JUSTIN MICHAEL WELLS

PHONE:

817-657-1989

E-MAIL:

jwellstx@gmail.com

ADDRESS:

220 Barton Creek Dr Dripping Springs, TX 78620

LinkedIn:

https:// www.linkedin.com/in/ jwellstx/

PORTFOLIO:

https:// jwellstx.github.io/ My_Portfolio/

SUMMARY

Electrical Engineer with 10+ years of experience working with product development, validation and manufacturing at Intel Corporation. Primarily focused in Python with expanded knowledge in web design and full stack development. Motivated problem solver, critical thinker and solution generator. Strengths include hardware development, web development, leadership and management.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Product Development Engineer - Software Development Intel Corporation, Austin TX — 2009-2016; 2018-Present

- -Develop and maintain tools to enable users to generate content for product manufacturing and validation
- -Proficient in pre-silicon regression, simulation, model testing and performing post silicon debug and execution

Product Development Engineer - Reset Owner Intel Corporation, Austin TX — 2016-2018

- Pre-silicon reset sequence development and validation using simulation and emulation. Experience includes designer collaboration to prepare for silicon power on and RTL debug.
- Post-silicon debug and validation for successful chip power on for Intel servers and client products

EDUCATION

University of Texas at Austin - B.S. Electrical Engineering, 2011 University of Texas at Austin Coding Bootcamp- *In Progress* (2020)

SKILLS



PATENTS

-Wells, J., Wessels C., and Rangel R. Embryo Selection System and Method of Use (Application # 62562639, filed September 25, 2017)